tinyowl.com 2016-05-04

# TinyOwl | Privacy Policy

#### Personal Information

User hereinafter referred to as (“You”) and TinyOwl Technology Pvt. Ltd. hereinafter referred to as (“TinyOwl”). TinyOwl is owner and operator of [www.tinyowl.com](http://www.tinyowl.com/) (“the Website”), TinyOwl’s Mobile Application for food ordering (“TinyOwl App”); collectively, including all content provided by TinyOwl through the TinyOwl App and the Website (“TinyOwl Service”).

You have right not to supply personally identifiable information. It is not mandatory to register however, the order placed by You will reach to You only when You disclose certain personal information. If You intend to view this TinyOwl Service and/or or share your data with the TinyOwl Service, it is solely at your own volition, risk and after reading and confirming it to this Privacy Policy.

At the time of using the TinyOwl Service you will share certain Personal Information with TinyOwl, TinyOwl respects your Personal Information. Such Personal Information may include your personal identifiable information such as your name, address, telephone, your e-mail ids, your age and any other personal information which You may share.

When you use TinyOwl’s Service through TinyOwl App, TinyOwl may use Your mobile device’s ID (the unique identification assigned to a mobile device by the manufacturer). TinyOwl does this to store your preferences and track your use of TinyOwl App. You understand and agree that TinyOwl has every right to share such ID with third parties for its promotions, analysis, etc.

In case You participate in any other schemes, facilities, services provided by the TinyOwl Service, You will be required to provide additional information. Such information will also remain in TinyOwl’s database and will be considered as your Personal Information and will be treated as confidential.

#### Protection of Information and Storage

TinyOwl needs to caution You that the TinyOwl Service could be vulnerable to hacking, virus attacks and your personal data may be at risk. TinyOwl takes reasonable caution to protect the TinyOwl Service and data.

#### Cookies

TinyOwl may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your Mobile. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable the TinyOwl Service to relate your use of the TinyOwl Service to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided to TinyOwl.

The Cookies enables TinyOwl to remember your choices and some data field contents which you would be required to fill-in.

#### Advertisements

On the TinyOwl App and/or the Website, TinyOwl posts advertisements provided by Advertisers. These Advertisers might set mobile device id on their Apps. TinyOwl is not responsible for any of these Advertisers. You on your entire risk and volition are advised to deal with the Advertisers if You intend to. By allowing such advertisements TinyOwl do not recommend or market or warranty the Advertisers, quality, commitment, deliverables, fitness to consumption, reasonability and Advertisers commitment to protect your Personal Information.

#### Pre-approved Sharing of Personal Information

TinyOwl endeavours to protect your Personal Information. TinyOwl may share your Personal Information with its sponsors, service providers and its business partners. Personal Information could be shared so that you may receive newsletters, offers, information about new products, services, launches, facilities, schemes and other information, if applicable. The information collected from You and other users may be analysed in different manners. TinyOwl may also share such analysis with its service providers and its business partners.

In case TinyOwl is required to disclose your Personal Information in order to assist the Government Authority or in adherence to the Court or to protect the interest of the TinyOwl Service and/or any particular user(s), TinyOwl will disclose it without obtaining prior permission from you.

#### Changes to Privacy Policy

TinyOwl have and continue to have the right to modify, change or update Privacy Policy at any time. However, TinyOwl will use your Personal Information in a manner consistent with Privacy Policy at the time you shared Personal Information. You are encouraged to check the TinyOwl Service often to get updated about Privacy Policy. You acknowledge that by virtue of usage of the TinyOwl Service you provide acceptance of the Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:Unit No.102 &103 1st Floor A Wing Supreme Business  
Park, Supreme City, Hiranandani Gardens, Powai  
Mumbai  
Maharashtra, INDIA  

This document was last updated on June 9, 2015
